Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A group of females of varying ages, with a small table set with food. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Birthdays; Children; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A family group in winter coats in the mountains in front of a sign "Seytanin Ayak Izi Dilek Tasi - Devil's stone of wishes" 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Ayvalik, Balikesir, Turkey; Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Nature; Photographic Prints; Seas; Women
- A young male and young female receiving a diploma/award from two older men on a stage. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Teachers; Turkey
- A youth in a striped shirt, posing with one hand on hip and one behind the head. 8.9 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two males in suits, walking on the street with large buildings in the background. 13.5 x 8.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Advertisements; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets; Suits; Walking
- A young male in a dark suit and a young female in a light jacket, in front of a painted backdrop. 14.0 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A young female and two older males, one with a knife cutting into a cake. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Couple; Eating; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A female in a light sleeveless dress and short hair with a moutain top settlement in the background. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Unknown Locations; Women
- A young male and a young female seated on ornate chairs. 8.5 x 14.5 cm, 3 November 1936; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A family group seated around a rectangular table with a tall stone wall and trees in the background. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Children; Fashion Accessories; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A bride seated in the corner of a room with three females embracing her. 8.6 x 14.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A group of older females in a classroom with a chalk board with writing in the background. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey; Women
- A group of young girls in white dresses on a stage with an older couple and flower arrangements. 9.8 x 14.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Children; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey
- A family group portrait with the bride and groom seated in the front row and flower arrrangements in the foreground. 9.1 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits
- A group of young men in military uniform gathered on the street in front of some stone buildings. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A bride in a dress and veil, standing with a female in front of some wooden chairs and a stone wall. 13.8 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Brides; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony
- A young girl in a dress and jacket, standing in a park. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A family group sitting behind a circular table with a large palm in the background. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Turkey
- A mixed group of males and females in winter coats standing in front of the Izmir Clock Tower. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 18 February 1948; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Head Covers; Izmir Clock Tower; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints
- An older male standing in his underwear in front of a door. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A family group standing in a garden. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A male and two older females standing on the side of a road with a horse drawn wagon approaching them. Antalya, Kamp, Turkey. 8.0 x 14.0 cm, July 1973; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Antalya, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horses; Photographic Prints; Streets; Women
- A bridge with a large updo sitting in a chair with an older woman holding her and a young child in the foreground. 14.1 x 8.8 cm, 16 October 1966; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Brides; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A woman in a white dress holding a baby. 8.7 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Births; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A group of school childern, standing in front of a building with a sign on it, "Namazgah Ilkokulu". 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Boys; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Teachers; Turkey; Uniforms
- A large group of young males in suits. A male in the middle right is wearing a white hat on his head. 8.8 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Boys; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey; Uniforms
- A group of young females in the same uniform and young males in suits, with buildings in the background. 8.8 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Turkey; Uniforms
- Young females in the same black dress with white collar, standing in front of a wood building with white bars on the windows. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young couple on their wedding day, standing on a flower patterned carpet with sheer curtains in the background. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 10 October 1968; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gloves; Isparta, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits
- A young male in military uniform with an anchor on his hat. 12.8 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms
- An older female and a younger male sitting on a coach with a lamp behind them. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young male standing in front of a doorway wearing a white shirt and shorts. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1976; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A group of five young children, one male wearing a fez and holding a walking stick and one female with an umbrella and a fan. 9.0 x 12.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Boys; Costumes; Fezes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Turkey
- A young male in a white outfit with a patterned cape, holding a bowl with flames in it. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Beds; Boys; Circumcisions; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young male wearing a white shirt with a sash and hat, under a flower patterned blanket. 8.4 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Beds; Boys; Circumcisions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- An older couple looking off camera to the left, female is wearing a houndstooth jacket. 11.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A young woman in a patterned skirt suit. Studio Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A group of young males in military uniform, taken from ground level. 8.9 x 14.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey
- A group of couples in formal attire with ballons overhead. 9.0 x 13.0 cm, 26 May 1979; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of males of varying ages in military uniform holding rifles. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Guns; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey; Uniforms
- A mixed group of school children at desks. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Houses; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Teachers; Turkey; Uniforms
- A bride and groom on the wedding day with some guests, flower arrangements in the background. 9.0 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of school aged children in uniform standing in front of old stone buildings. 8.7 x 12.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Houses; Photographic Prints; Students; Turkey; Uniforms
- A bride with flowers in her hands, standing with two males in suits, one with a tie and one with a bowtie. Foto Luks, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.4 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Luks, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits
- A bride and groom, bride is holding a bouquet of flowers with two large flower arrangements on the floor in front. Istanbul, Turkey. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 1 September 1962; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits
- A bride on her wedding day with two women hugging her. 9.1 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A group of men sitting at square tables, some in military dress whites. 8.9 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Alcohol; Drinking; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey
- A profile of a young female in a white dress, with a small necklace on and a shoulder length hair cut. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A bride and groom on their wedding day, standing with another couple in front of an old wooden building and a stone wall. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits
- A large group of males and females at a large banquet table in a room with wood columns. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Boys; Circumcisions; Drinking; Eating; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Five women in western clothes behind the desk in an office. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Calenders; Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A male in a dark vest holding a baby in a sweater. 9.0 x 12.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two older females, one in a black jacket and one in a patterened turtleneck. Studio Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.3 x 13.1 cm, 6 January 1979; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young couple on the deck of a boat with water and some buildings behind them. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, June 1952; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Steamboats; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A family group in the countryside, next to a river. Turkish writing. 9.0 x 12.8 cm, 6 July 1952; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Countryside; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A young couple, male is wearing what looks like a Boy Scout uniform, female is wearing a pinstripped jacket. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, 6 July 1962; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young man standing with his hands on his hips on a tree lined street with some houses in the background. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Countryside; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets; Turkey
- Three young males in white outfits behind a desk with a leather bag on it. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, 16 April 1968; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms
- A group of males dressed in military uniform lined up for inspection. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey
- A group of males in military uniform in the sand. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Guns; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey
- A large group of males in military uniform, with hoops on their caps. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Rekor Universite, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Three males in military uniform and a fourth wearing a fez. Foto Ankara, Kütahya, Turkey. 8.6 x 13.8 cm, 1950; Studio Foto Ankara, Kutahya, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Kutahya, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography
- A group of young males in sports uniform on a dirt football pitch. One male is holding a football. 8.6 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Countryside; Footballs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Turkey
- A group of males in white shirts and shorts and some in winter clothes. A seated male is holding a dog. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Dogs; Footballs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Turkey
- A young child in winter clothes, standing in the snow outside a stone building. Sarikamis, Kars, Turkey. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 10 April 1960; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kars, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Snow
- A bride and groom seated around a table, with some guests with flowers on it. 9.0 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony
- An older male with two younger males and a small barking dog in front of a place and flowers. Feast of the Sacrifice. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, 1963; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Children; Dogs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young girl in a black and gold traditional outfit with red curtains in the background. 12.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Color Photography; Costumes; Furnishings; Girls; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Turkey
- An older female in a dress feeding a man reclining in the grass next to trees. 9.3 x 11.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Couple; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two males in military uniform with a young boy sitting in a car. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Boys; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey
- A male in a military hat and winter coat, holding a leather bag and gloves in a winter landscape. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Military; Parks; Photographic Prints; Snow; Turkey
- Males in military uniform sitting at a table eating and drinking. 8.7 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Drinking; Eating; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms
- Children in school uniform and their teachers standing on the stairs of a building. 8.8 x 12.4 cm, 25 May 1958; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Boy Scouts; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Teachers; Turkey; Uniforms
- A couple and their son at the beach in bathing suits. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Males in military uniform seated in couches around a round wooden table with an ashtray on it. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Military; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms
- Two men with toothbrush mustaches seated behind a small wooden table with a large piece of machinery behind them. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
- A couple, female in a light top with a small flower at the top button, male is wearing a light suit with a tie. Foto Uslu. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, 28 October 1980; Studio Foto Uslu, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Four females of varying ages seated around a dinner table laided with food and bottles. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Drinking; Eating; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young male in a white short suit, with a sash and hat. Studio Ideal. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Studio Ideal Fotograf Studyosu (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Boys; Circumcisions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- Two males and one female in bathing suits sitting at the beach. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two males next to an older female in a flower dress seated in a chair. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Family; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Turkey
- Two young males in Western dress, standing in front of a photographic backdrop of a river scene. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young female in a light dress with a large flower at the breast, having adjustments made by an older covered woman. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Men in military hats and long winter coats standing in front of a train car. 8.8 x 11.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trains; Turkey; Uniforms
- A bride with a large veil with two females and a male in a double breasted suit. Foto Yalim, Bursa, Turkey. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Yalim, Bursa, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Bursa, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits
- Four females in white lab coats sitting on a bench next to a fountain surrounded by plants. 8.8 x 12.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms; Women
- A couple and two young males in matching outfits of white shirts with sashes and hat, sitting with books on their laps. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Beds; Books; Boys; Circumcisions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young child with a white sweat suit and a shirt with snowflakes on it, next to an inflatable duck. Turkish writing on the front. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 1 May 1967; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Toys; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A shirtless male, flexing with some mountains in the background. 9.1 x 12.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Four females seated a table with food and cake on it. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Alcohol; Birthdays; Calenders; Drinking; Eating; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A family group gathered around a table with a large birthday cake with candles in the middle. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Birthdays; Eating; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- An older female in a dress, with two younger females in pants, standing on a balcony with buildings in the background. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 1970; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A male and a female on the dance floor, female is sitting in a shiny skirt and short top with blonde hair. 8.8 x 13.5 cm, June 1972; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Women
- Two males in suits, one with a mustache and a female in a black outfit with a large white collar and a updo. Foto Güzel. 9.0 x 13.8, Undated; Studio Foto Guzel, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Two young females, one in pants and a light striped top. Studyo Serdar, Ankara, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm., Undated; Studio Serdar, Ankara, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A group of females of varying ages. Seated veiled female with glasses, on the far left. 8.4 x 13.4 cm, 19 November 1942; Studio Foto Kemal, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms; Women
- Young couple. Female is wearing a black dress and choker, male is in a light suit with a diagonally stripped tie. Foto Moda. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Moda, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Three young males in suits and tie and one female wearing a plaid vest. Osmancik, Corum, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 8 May 1969; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Corum, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Women
- A group of couples in a bar with a large mosaic tiled pillar. 11.5 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Alcohol; Bars; Cigarettes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A large family group in a living room. Older female in the front row in a flower patterned dress holding a black purse. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Young females in the same black dress with white collars standing in front of some large trees and bushes. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Students; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young male in a white tux jacket sitting in a chair and a military cap on the table next to him. 8.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey
- Two older females, one in a floral patterned dress and a young female between them in a white dress with a large white bow on her head. Studio Suat. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Suat, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 12)
- A group of school children in white clothes standing on the stairs of a building with large windows. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey
- A family group with two young males in white shirts. Foto Bilsen. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Bilsen, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 12)
- A young female in a light skirt suit with a small black purse on her left arm. Studio Gorcek. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 12)
- A male in a dark pin stripped suit. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.4 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 5, Folder 12)
- A couple seated on a dark sofa, male is wearing a bow tie. 9.3 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Females gathered around a rectangular table eating a meal. 8.2 x 12.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women